## — SYEFIRA SHOFA ←

MARKETING ANALYST

### **CONTACT**

- (818) 736-1863
- sshofa@sandiego.edu
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/syefira-shofa/
- https://sshofa.github.io

### **PROFILE**

Technical Marketing Analyst with a Mathematics background experienced in the video game, consumer electronics and genealogy industries. Familiar with various marketing channels spanning throughout all parts of the marketing funnel. Adept at developing ETL's, mathematical and statistical modeling, and performance reporting.

### **SKILLS**

#### Computing

SQL, R, Python

#### **Analytics Tools**

Apache Airflow, GitHub, GitLab, Databricks, AWS Redshift & S3, Tableau, Datorama, Microsoft Power BI

### **Marketing Channels**

Offline TV, Audio, Display & Video, Programmatic, Social, Search, In-Game Communication, Email, Push, SMS

## EDUCATION & TRAINING

# Georgia Institute of Technology

MicroMasters, Analytics: Essential Tools & Methods

Anticipated Completion: May 2021

## University of San Diego

Bachelor of Arts, Mathematics

Minors: International Business & Asian Studies

### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Marketing Analyst**

Activision, 2020-Present

- Conducted statistical modeling to investigate marketing impact on player engagement and company revenue
- Analyzed performance of marketing efforts and worked cross-functionally to implement optimization recommendations
- Owned automated dashboard ETL, continuously adding/refining models for deeper understanding of campaigns and optimized code for efficiency

### Associate Marketing Science Manager

OMD, 2019-2020

Account: Apple, Ancestry

- Designed, tested, deployed and optimized automated data process with data coming in from multiple data sources across all media channels on a global scale
- Developed RMarkdown reporting templates for automated reporting
- Developed Recursive Partitioning model to identify best audience grouping for benchmarks
- Developed flighting strategy to optimize media allocation throughout the new fiscal year
- Developed match market test statistical methodology to test effectiveness of new marketing tactic

### **Analyst**

MediaCom, 2018-2019

Account: PlayStation

- Rebuilt the database, optimized the data process and improved naming conventions
- Developed and automated business intelligence dashboards for data visualization and insight generation
- Connected excel to SQL database, allowing internal teams to obtain data in real time and analyze with customized data for reporting